https://www.gale.com/privacy

Cengage Privacy Overview
Simply put, your privacy is our priority.
We know you use Cengage products and services to learn—to build the knowledge, skills and confidence you need to succeed. You can trust that Cengage will always handle your personal information respectfully and responsibly so that you can interact with us in confidence.
All Cengage companies are bound by our Global Privacy Program, which protects the personal information we receive from you as well as information we receive from schools and other third parties. It protects information collected online as well as offline. It reflects our Core Privacy Principles.
View our Complete Privacy Notice
DOWNLOAD AS A PDF VERSION >
×
Loading ...
Our Core Customer Privacy Principles
1. We want you to know how we handle your personal information.
We are committed to being transparent with you about how we handle your personal information. The Cengage Privacy Notice explains how and why we collect, use and disclose your information. You can always contact us at privacy@cengage.com if you have any other questions.
×
Loading ...
2. We are committed to improving learning experiences while protecting privacy.
We only use personal information as needed to achieve specific educational and business goals. We use your data in ways that we believe will enhance your learning experience and improve your outcomes. For example, we use your information to help personalize the Cengage digital learning platforms you use, making your study time more efficient and effective. When we use your usage data to help improve our learning products and services to better serve all students, we do so in a way that is aggregated and anonymized.
×
Loading ...
3. We never sell student data.
We never sell student marketing lists. We only share personal information with third parties as need to provide services to you and to the schools we serve, with your consent, and for permitted business purposes, such as in connection with mergers and acquisitions or legal compliance.
Gale, a Cengage company, publishes business directories. These directories contain publicly-available business contact information about corporate executives, academics and professionals obtained from third party sources, such as company websites, publications, public records providers and other commercial sources. We respect the rights of professionals to opt-out of having their business contact information included in these directories. To opt out, click here.
×
Loading ...
4. We respect your choices about how we use your information.
We respect your right to opt out of our marketing communications. You can always opt-out of emails by clicking the link labeled “unsubscribe” at the bottom of any email we send you, or by contacting our Customer Service department by email: optout@cengage.com, or phone: +1 800.354.9706 (M - F, 8:00 am – 6:00 pm ET). To revoke permissions that you may have given to send text messages, text STOP in response to any message.
Cengage also respects your right to access, correct and request deletion or restriction of your personal information as required by law.
The Cengage Privacy Notice tells you how to exercise your rights. You may also contact us via email to privacy@cengage.com and a member of our Privacy Team will assist you.
If you believe that we have processed your Personal Information in violation of applicable law, you may file a complaint with the Cengage Privacy Office or with the appropriate supervisory authority.
×
Loading ...
5. We are committed to protecting the privacy of schoolchildren.
The personal information we process about K-12 students belongs to the schools we service. We do not use any identifiable K-12 student data for our purposes. We also do not allow any children under the age of 16 to register with Cengage directly. We encourage parents and teachers to spend time online with children and to monitor their online activities. You can learn more about our commitment to children’s’ privacy in our Privacy Statement Regarding K-12 Students and Children’s Data.
×
Loading ...
6. We are committed to keeping your information secure.
We take the security of your personal information seriously and understand that your trust depends on our protecting it. We are committed to protecting your information against unauthorized access or loss.
×
Loading ...
Additional Privacy Program Information
Privacy Statement Regarding K-12 Students and Children’s Data
Important Information for Residents of California
Important Information for Residents of the EEA, Switzerland and the UK
Important Information for Residents of Brazil
Cengage Cookies Notice
Cengage Applicant Privacy Notice
Important Information for Residents of Canada
Our collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information is done on the basis of your consent (implied or express) or where otherwise permitted or required by the laws of Canada, including the laws of the applicable province. You imply your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information as described in the Cengage Privacy Notice where you provide your Personal Information to us or use our Services and have access to the Cengage Privacy Notice or as described in any other privacy notice that you may be given when your Personal Information is collected. We will process any request from you to access, correct, or delete your Personal Information under the appropriate Canadian law.
Privacy Statement for Hosted School Websites
Certain Cengage businesses, like Ed2Go, administer websites that provide course materials and services for educational institutions and companies. Information collected on these websites is only used by us to support our clients and provide the services requested by the course instructors. We do not use this information for our own purposes. Most educational institution student course records are also protected by the Family and Educational Rights Privacy Act (FERPA). For information on your company or school's privacy policies, please contact the administration.
Our hosted websites may offer students and professionals the opportunity to interact directly with Cengage Learning. If so, the Cengage Privacy Notice will apply to that information.
Social Security Number Policy Statement
Cengage Learning, Inc. and its affiliates collect U.S. Social Security numbers and other sensitive Personal Information in the ordinary course of its business. We have implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative safeguards to help protect sensitive Personal Information from unlawful use and unauthorized disclosure. All Cengage workers are required to follow these established safeguards, which include the following:
Access to sensitive Personal Information is limited to those workers and service providers who have a need to access the information to perform tasks for Cengage. Sensitive Personal Information is only disclosed to third parties in accordance with Cengage's established privacy and security policies.
Cengage will only disclose sensitive Personal Information (1) to those service providers, auditors, advisors and/or successors in interest who are legally or contractually obligated to protect them, or (2) as required or permitted by law.
If you have any questions, please contact us at privacy@cengage.com.
View Our Complete Privacy Notice
DOWNLOAD AS A PDF VERSION >
